{
    "subject": "resource/Scoop_(2006_film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Hugh_Jackman",
    "human_readable": "Hugh Jackman stars in the 2006 film Scoop.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9306549429893494,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie starring Hugh Jackman in 2006?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9275984764099121,
            "question": "In what film did Hugh Jackman appear in 2006?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.913440465927124,
            "question": "Who starred in the 2006 film Scoop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8717257380485535,
            "question": "What role did Hugh Jackman likely play in Scoop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5957648754119873,
            "question": "Are there any other famous films starring Hugh Jackman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5493605136871338,
            "question": "Is Hugh Jackman known for acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4391886293888092,
            "question": "What year was the film Scoop released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3344186842441559,
            "question": "What genre is the film Scoop likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17448949813842773,
            "question": "Would you recommend watching Scoop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16900849342346191,
            "question": "Can you name another movie released in 2006?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hugh Jackman stars in the 2006 film Scoop.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8275_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Would you recommend watching Scoop?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8275_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Scoop likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8275_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the film Scoop released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8275_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8275_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8275_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8275_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8275_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8275_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8275_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8275_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8275_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8275_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8275_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The context information includes multiple mentions of Hugh Jackman starring in the 2006 film \"Scoop\", and Woody Allen directing and writing the film, which also stars Hugh Jackman alongside Scarlett Johansson."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that confirms Hugh Jackman starred in the 2006 film \"Scoop,\" directed by Woody Allen. This is directly supported by multiple entries within the context, such as document 80.txt and 14.txt."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}